ondesoft.com 2017-12-11

# Ondesoft Corporation - Privacy Policy

Home > Ondesoft Customer Privacy Policy

When you visit our website, purchase Ondesoft products and services, or when you contact our sales or supporting colleagues, Ondesoft 's collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information occurs.

Please pay attention to the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy, including the types of information that are gathered, the purposes of the gathered information, to whom we disclose the information, and how we protect your personal information. Your privacy is of great importance at Ondesoft, and we persistently spare no effort to protect it. 

**Why we collect personal information**

* * *

Your personal information will help us provide a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services. In addition, your personal information makes it possible for us to remind you the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about. 

**What information we collect**

* * *

For your access to better products or service, such kinds of information is useful to us:

When you interact with Ondesoft, we may ask your personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences, your credit card information and information about the Ondesoft products you own, such as their serial numbers and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue.

We also collect information for market research and analysis—such as your occupation and where you use your computer—to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. 

**When we collect your personal information**

* * *

We may ask for your personal information when you're discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product. 

**How we use your personal information**

* * *

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Ondesoft's latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don't want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by updating your preferences.

Your personal information helps us to determine how to provide more useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and services are of most interest to them.

We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the Ondesoft Corporation globally who will take steps to safeguard it consistent with Ondesoft's privacy policy.

There are also times when it may be advantageous for Ondesoft to make certain personal information about you available to strategic partners that work with Ondesoft to provide products and services, or that help Ondesoft market to customers. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with Ondesoft's policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary. 

**How we protect your personal information**

* * *

Ondesoft takes precautions—including administrative, technical, and physical measures— to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Ondesoft uses secure server hosted by PayPal, SWREG and other third party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

**Cookies and other technologies**

* * *

Ondesoft's website uses "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons to tell us which parts of our website people have visited, facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not tell who you are, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Ondesoft will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

**Anti-malware statement**

* * *

Ondesoft strongly objects all forms of malware. Ondesoft applications will never intentionally endanger our customers' privacy or security. All applications are designed to be easily removable from the computer through an uninstall utility. 

No Ondesoft application is designed to collect any personally identifiable information from any user’s computer.

Ondesoft applications do not contain, nor are they bundled with, any third party applications (spyware, adware, malware, etc.) that would jeopardize our customers' security or their privacy.

All Ondesoft applications pass both Kaspersky and Rising vigorous anti-virus/malware tests before public release.

**Integrity and Retention of Personal Information**

* * *

Ondesoft makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**Privacy Questions**

* * *

If you have any questions or concerns about Ondesoft’s Privacy Policy, please contact us.  
Ondesoft may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.
